Joe Ulyatt

Software Engineer

Technical Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- PHP
- Bootstrap
- Node.is
- Express.js
- jQuery
- AJAX
- React.js
- MongoDB
- Mongoose
- Git
- API's
- WordPress

<u>Telephone</u> +44 7891 870311

GitHub

Github.com/joewhocodes

<u>Portfolio Website</u> Joewhocodes.co.uk

Email

JoeWhoCodes@gmail.com

<u>Location</u>

Austin, TX

Education

Southampton Solent Uni 2:1 Music Production

Oxford Cherwell College AAA Music Tech

<u>References</u>

Available on request

<u>Interests</u>

Making electronic music, Building digital synthesizers Anything creative!

Personal Statement

Hey, I'm Joe, a full-stack Software Engineer with a passion for developing apps that help people.

With over a decade's worth of experience in the Audio Engineering world, I've always kept myself at the forefront of emerging digital technologies. From building rental management platforms to photography portfolios, my creative edge and ever-expanding skillset are omnipresent in the apps and websites I'm a part of.

I'm competent with MERN stack, JS, HTML, CSS, Git and MVC structures, and invite you to explore examples of my work on the listed channels.

Experience

100 Devs – Software Developer

Oct 2021 – Present

- Collaborating with a team of developers to build modern and responsive web applications using best practices
- Building semantically structured full stack web applications
- Applying agile methodologies like SCRUM for project management

Freelance - Software Developer

Nov 2021 - Present

- Creating client websites using JS, JQuery, Bootstrap, CSS & HTML
- Building passion project apps using the MERN stack

King Sound Reinforcement – Technical Operations

Feb 2017 to Nov 2021 - Bristol

- Managing Current RMS software of over 4000 hire items
- Creation of rental arm of website pulling from the Current RMS Database
- Creating client quote templates using HTML, CSS and vanilla JS
- Lead AV Technician for live-streamed corporate conferences and live events

<u>Apps</u>

JarJam

MERN Stack Application that connects you with other music players in your area for jam sessions.

MovieGoJoe

FullStack Application that pulls data from MovieDatabase API, which allows you to check out the latest movie trailers and add them to a watchlist.

KingSR Hire

FullStack E-Commerce Application that allows you to hire from a list of over 4000 rental items.

The Burrows Bed & Breakfast

FrontEnd E-Commerce Website with fully integrated booking system.